Aditya Vishwakarma

6339 Bollinger Road Cupertino, CA 95014

(408) 582-3754

aditya1vishwakarma@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Motivated and hard-working International Business student at University of California, San Diego with the best interest of myself and my community in mind. Through a desire to get things done, I've worked and volunteered at numerous places developing valuable skills as part of a team.

EDUCATION .

De Anza College, Cupertino, CA UC San Diego, La Jolla, CA [B.A International Business]

Deans List at De Anza College, Cumulative GPA across colleges: 3.0

KEY SKILLS -

Communication, Team work, Microsoft Excel, Final Cut Pro, Accounting with Quickbooks

EXPERIENCE

April 2017 – December 2019 Intern • Media producer • Environmental Sustainability Committee

August 2017 – November 2017 Sales Associate • Part-Time • Staples Inc.

January 2018 – October 2018
Part-Time Accountant Billing Statements Viable Consulting

September 2018 – September 2019 | September 2020 - Present Editor • Co-Founder/Producer • Luminous Moments Photography

COMMUNICATION

Helped save the free bus program for my community college with the Environmental Sustainability Committee at De Anza College. Involved going to city hall and presenting our case to local leaders.

LEADERSHIP

Directed, Edited and Acted in short films and informational videos for the Environmental Sustainability Committee at De Anza College to advertise programs we had to offer.

Started photography side-business with a friend to explore creative vision and expand skills with a camera

REFERENCES

Kadhirash Sivakumar, Colleague at Staples and classmate at De Anza, 2 years: kadhirash@gmail.com | Cell: (408) 759-0836